golfballed.com 2018-12-25

# Privacy Policy

**GOLFBALLED.COM**

**PRIVACY POLICY**

The GolfBalled.com Privacy Policy describes how we collect and use personal information submitted by website visitors or obtained by us when users enter and interact with the website. By using the GolfBalled.com website you demonstrate your agreement to be bound by this Privacy Policy.

**Information Collected By GolfBalled.com**

Personal Information: You can browse our site without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. Some services may require the user to register with the website. Once you have given us your personal information, through the registration process, you are no longer anonymous to us. In such cases personal information, including but not limited to your name, email address, and password, will be collected. Other services may require you to submit addition information.

Cookies: When you visit GolfBalled.com we send cookies to your computer. Cookies are used to identify your browser and IP address. Among other things, cookies may be used for storing user preferences, improving search results, providing relevant advertisements, and tracking user trends. While most browsers are configured to accept cookies you can reset your browser to refuse cookies or to manually accept them. However, if you disable cookies it may affect your ability to use the GolfBalled.com website as designed. 

Log Information: When you enter the GolfBalled.com website its servers record the information sent by your browser. Information such as your web request, IP address, browser type and language, the date and time of your request, and cookies that may identify your browser are logged into the servers. 

User Communications: When you send an email to GolfBalled.com we may keep this communication to facilitate the processing of your request, respond to you, or improve our services.

Links: The GolfBalled.com website may include links in a format designed to allow us to determine whether the links have been followed. We do this to improve the quality of our search application and to customize content and advertising.

Gadgets: GolfBalled.com may make third party applications available through its services. The information collected when you enable a gadget is processed in accordance with this Privacy Policy and information gathered by the application or gadget provider is governed by their privacy policy.

**Usage Information**

When you enter the GolfBalled.com website information about your usage and any information you display about yourself as well as information you click on may be recorded. If you are logged into your GolfBalled.com account, such information may be associated with your account. 

**Content Uploaded to Site**

Any personal information or content that you voluntarily disclose online, including anything you post in the Forum/Golf Chat area of the website may be collected and used by others. You are advised and encouraged to post responsibly. 

**Other Uses for Personal Information**

Personal information provided by you may also be used for the following purposes: to improve services, including customized content and advertising; for research; for analysis and auditing; to ensure technical performance; to develop new applications or services and to protect the rights of GolfBalled.com and its users.

**Note** : This Privacy Policy applies to GolfBalled.com only. We have no control over other websites whose links may appear on our pages. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer should you choose to visit them. They may also collect other data or request personal information from you. We encourage our users to read the privacy policies of any website they visit.

**Sharing Information**

GolfBalled.com does not sell, rent, share, or otherwise disclose to others user information except as described in this document. GolfBalled.com may share information with our partners or affiliates under common control with GolfBalled.com. In some circumstances GolfBalled.com may share information as follows:

GolfBalled.com will disclose account and personal information at our discretion when we believe releasing such information is necessary to comply with or assist law enforcement or the legal process. GolfBalled.com strictly enforces our Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy in order to protect our users, others, and the GolfBalled.com website.

**Account Protection**

Your password is the key to your account. We encourage users to create unique passwords utilizing a combination of numbers and letters. Do not disclose your GolfBalled.com password to anyone. If you do share your password or other personal information with others, be informed that you are responsible for all actions taken in the name of your account. If you lose control of your password, you may lose control over your personal information and may be held accountable for legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if you suspect your password has been compromised, you should immediately notify GolfBalled.com and change your password.

**Security**

Your information is stored on our secured servers, which are located in the United States. We treat data as a valuable asset and protect it against unauthorized access and disclosure using tools such as encryption, passwords, and physical security. However, you should be aware that third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, and other users may abuse or misuse personal information that they collect from the site. Therefore, although we work to protect your privacy, we cannot ensure, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private. 

**Notification of Changes**

GolfBalled.com reserves the right to change, update or revise the terms of this Policy, and/or impose new conditions, policies or additional rules at any time without further notice to you. Therefore, we suggest you check periodically to see if there have been any changes to the Privacy Policy. The date of the most current version will appear on the last page of the document. Any such changes, together with the remainder of any unaltered provisions of this Privacy Policy will constitute GolfBalled.com’s Privacy Policy at the time of such notice and will be effective immediately upon posting. Your continued use of the GolfBalled.com Website following posting or notification of any such changes shall serve as your acceptance of these changes and your agreement to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.

**Children Under 13 Years**

GolfBalled.com does not knowingly collect information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are under age 13 you may not use this Website. If a User believes that we have information from or about a child under age 13 they should contact us immediately.

Revised:04/10/2012
